Privacy Policy
==============

In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. DBA Originals reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.

We do not sell or share email addresses or other personal information.

Credit card information is not stored on DBA Originals’ website database. All retail credit card transactions are forwarded to a secure financial gateway.

We collect an IP address from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site, and deliver customized, personalized content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  We DO NOT share this information. 

Copyright © 2024 DBA Originals | Powered by [Woostify](https://woostify.com/)

Search...

×

Type to search

Search...

×

#### Shopping cart

0

image/svg+xml

No products in the cart.

[_×_](javascript:void(0);)
